Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 14.07.25 07:57:14
www.tvsubtitles.net
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=- 时间轴微调:-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组 时间轴组=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
反恐24小时 第一季 第十五集
恐怖份子正密谋 暗杀总统候选人
(Jack) Right now, terrorists are plotting to assassinate a presidential candidate,
我的妻女双双遭到绑架
my wife and daughter are in danger,
而我的同事 可能同时牵涉这两件事
and people that l work with may be involved in both.
我是联邦探员杰克鲍尔
l'm FederalAgent Jack Bauer,
今天将是 我这辈子最长的一天
and this is the longest day ofmy life.
以下是发生在 下午两点至三点的事
美国总统大选加州初选当天
我不容你这般无礼
l can go over your head, Mr Almeida.
一切后果你自行负责
And l assure you, there will be consequences.
对不起 可是我们得遵守规定
l apologise, Senator, but we do have protocol.
我们的主管查裴尔 正在准备您的通行证
Our director, Ryan Chapelle, is working on a clearance.
-我会告诉他... -告诉他我要和鲍尔讲话
- But if l could tell him why you're here... - All he needs to know is l need to see Bauer.
而且是现在
And l need to do it now.
您等待的时候 是否需要...?
- Can l get you anything while...? - No.
我档不住他了 他要知道为何不能见杰克
Chapelle.
l don't think l can stall him much longer. He wants to know why he can't see Jack.
你怎么回答?
What did you tell him?
我说还有些事情要处里
Well, l told him you were workin' on it.
-他还是没有说明来意 -没有，他只说要见杰克
- And he still didn't say why he was here? - No. He just wants to see Jack.
没有进一步资讯 不能让他们俩见面
Well, until l know more, l don't wanna put those two together.
我再查一查
- l'm checking it out now. - All right.
-查出派默为何来这里了吗? -还没有
- So? You find out what Palmer's doin' here? - Not yet.
-其他的杀手相关情报呢? -有一个，叫艾力西斯杜瑞森
- Any new intel on the backup shooters? - Yeah, uh, an Alexis Drazen.
看来他与另两名杀手有关 但周六到达洛杉矶前
Looks like he's connected to two other shooters, but he stopped in DC for two days
他曾在华盛顿 停留了两天
before landing in LAX on Saturday.
还有些疑点 我要查清楚
There's other inconsistencies. l'm working on it.
-报告呢? -送到妮娜的电脑了
- Where's the report? - l routed it to Nina's computer.
也给我一份
- Send me a copy, would ya? - Yeah.
我们不是该到杰克的办公室 去回答一些问题的吗?
Weren't we supposed to answer some questions at Jack's office?
-到安全地点就会做 -我爸会到那里去吗?
- We're gonna do that at the safe house now. - ls my dad gonna be there?
还不会 可能等他离开反恐小组
Not right away. Maybe when he's done at CTU.
-妮娜，一切可好? -一切都好
- Are we OK, Nina? - Everything's fine.
受监控的环境 对你们是最安全的
A small, controlled environment is the most secure place for you.
-杰克知道我们要去的地方吗? -当然了
- Does Jack know you're taking us? - Of course. Myers.
我们要把泰莉和琴送到 安全地点，快到了
We're moving Teri and Kim to the safe house now. We should be there soon.
妈，你都不讲 医生说了什么
Mom...
you never told me what the doctor said.
(Nina) No, l'm not worried about that.
有个囊泡爆裂了
lt was a cyst that burst.
她说不严重
She said it wasn't serious.
没什么大不了的
- Then why did she...? - There's nothing to worry about.
她说这自己会好
She said it would go away all by itself.
甘恩斯曾打电话给我
Gaines first contacted me on my cellphone,
叫我走到一部 停在圣马克医院旁车子
directing me to a car parked at St Mark's Hospital.
-车子里面有收发器吗? -有，他要我戴在耳朵里
- The transmitter was in the car? - That's when he asked me to put it in my ear.
可以帮我查查 我老婆女儿在医院的情形吗
Can we take a break? Could you find out how my wife and daughter are doing at the clinic?
她们已经离开了
- Teri and Kim have already left the clinic. - What?
她们很好 妮娜要她们到安全地点
They're fine. Nina's moving them to a safe house.
你知道她们要被送走了 却不告诉我
You knew they were moving my wife and daughter and you didn't tell me?
够了，我不讲了
That's it. This is over.
我一个字也不说了 让我跟查裴尔讲话
l don't say another word. l wanna speak to Chapelle.
就是现在
Now, Alberta!
你太累了
You're exhausting.
昨晚接到你电话 真叫我吃惊
l was surprised you called last night.
我以为华盛顿那次后 我们不会再见
l didn't think l'd see you again after DC.
我可没那么容易甩掉
l'm not really that easy, you know.
你还会再休假吗
Will you have another break later in the day?
参议员今天下午就要走了 要到内华达州去
The senator has to leave town this afternoon, and he's going to... Nevada.
只有我们几个人知道而已 我是其中必须跟随的人之一
Only a few of us were told about it, and l am one of the ones who has to go with him.
-你得紧紧跟着他吗? -可以这么说
- You have to hold his hand? - ln so many words.
到了内华达你会有空吗?
Would it be too much to hope that you might have some free time in Nevada?
你想一起去吗?
You would wanna come?
要是你让我去的话
lf you want me.
浴室很大 两个人可以一起洗
This is a pretty big shower. There's room enough for two.
我马上就过来
l'm on my way.
我可以为你做什么吗?
- Alan. - Senator Palmer, what can l do foryou?
我想要跟反恐小组 一个叫杰克鲍尔的人讲话
l'm trying to talk to a CTU agent named Jack Bauer.
-你在哪里? -在反恐小组，洛杉矶
- Where are you? - CTU, Los Angeles.
他们说要有证件 但是我已经等得太久了
They say l need clearance, but it's taking forever.
-那里是谁在做主的? -雷恩查裴尔
- Not a problem. Who's in charge over there? - Ryan Chapelle.
我马上处里
Yeah. OK, l'll take care ofthis right away.
谢谢，亚伦 算我欠你的
Thank you, Alan. l owe you.
参议员派默先生 我是雷恩查裴尔
Senator Palmer, Ryan Chapelle.
有什么问题吗? 我为何不能见探员鲍尔?
What seems to be the problem, Ryan? Why can't l get in to see Agent Bauer?
当探员接受 内部侦讯的时候
Please forgive the wait. When an agent is under internal investigation,
我们有规定在问话结束之前 必须被隔离
procedure is to keep him isolated until he's been fully interrogated.
这不是我规定的
lt's... really out of my hands.
要是我对你们的侦讯 会有帮助呢
Even if l can help you with your investigation?
查裴尔先生，国防部 亚伦澳普提肯先生来电
Mr Chapelle? Alan Optican from the Pentagon's on the line for you.
对不起
Excuse me.
我是澳普提肯 国防部的人
- Chapelle. - This is Optican, Department ofDefense.
你要马上处里参议员 派默先生所有需要做的事情
Yes, sir.
Senator Palmer is to be given carte blanche. Make sure he gets whatever he needs.
-听懂了没? -当然，长官
- Yes, sir. - Understood?
- Of course, sir. - Thankyou.
马上带杰克鲍尔过来
Bring Jack Bauer down here right away.
谢谢你帮我 把繁文缛节都省掉了
Thanks... for helping me... cut through the red tape.
把所有摄影和录音设备 都关掉
Mm-hm.
l want all your cameras and recording equipment shut down.
我要私下与他谈谈
This is going to be a private conversation.
我了解，我会确保 这房间不受打扰
l understand. l'll make sure the room is secure.
Thank you.
- Hey, Jack. - Hey.
妮娜来电 说泰莉和琴都很好
Listen, Nina called and wanted me to tell you that Teri and Kim are fine.
-谁负责那里的安全 -保罗森与布瑞赫
- Who's guardin' the house? - Paulson and Breeher.
查裴尔找你 到会议室里去
OK, good.
Also, Chapelle wants to see you in the conference room.
Good.
东尼，谢谢
- Thanks a lot, Tony. - You got it.
抱歉我把那张卡片调包了 我别无选择
Milo, l'm sorry l had to switch the cards on you last night. l had no choice.
我们了解你的处境
We understand what you were goin' through.
谢谢帮忙
Thanks for your help.
Senator Palmer.
你走吧
Leave us.
我会在外面
- l'll be outside. - Thank you.
关门
Close the door.
坐
Sit.
好的
Yes, sir.
我想知道 你和谁一夥的
l wanna know who's working with you.
-长官，什么意思? -不必多说
- ln which context, sir? l'm sorry, l don't... - Right here, right now. We're gonna end this.
-我不懂你想要... -我知道你为何要杀我
- l don't know what they told you... - l know why you want me dead.
我听不懂你的意思
- l don't know what you're talking about. - Kosovo!
科索沃
我知道到今天你仍怀恨 我在两年前让你的属下牺牲了
- Kosovo? - l know you hold me responsible
for the men you lost there two years ago today.
-你知道有关暗夜计画的事? -那是我授权的任务
- You know about Operation Nightfall? - l authorised the mission.
我知道你攻入了维克多杜瑞森 内部，而且六个下属都阵亡了
l know you took out Victor Drazen and his inner circle. And lost six men in the process.
所以你以为我要报仇?
- And you think l want revenge? - Yes, l do.
今天我为了保护你 差点没命
With all due respect, l almost died today trying to protect you.
我的人在科索夫阵亡 都怪我自己
And if l blame anyone for the death of my men in Kosovo, l blame myself.
那你今天在发电厂做什么?
- What were you doin' at the power plant? - l was trying to...
我会去抢那探员的枪
The reason l went for that agent's gun, sir,
是因为我得在保全自己的情况下 让你安全的离开那里
was to try and get you out of the room without giving myself away.
想要杀你的人 绑架了我的家人
The people that want you dead had kidnapped my family.
他们威胁我协助暗杀 不然就要杀害她们
They threatened to kill them if l didn't assist them in the assassination attempt.
你到这边来他们没有 告诉过你这些事情对不对
They didn't tell you any of this when you came in, did they, sir?
No.
是真的 你去问问查裴尔
lt's the truth. You can verify it with Chapelle.
她们刚刚抵达安全地点了
- OK, they're just arriving at the safe house. - (man) Copy that. Show visual.
This way, Mrs Bauer.
这是探员保罗森与布里赫 他们与杰克共事多年
These are Agents Paulson and Breeher. They've worked with Jack for many years.
这是杰克的太太泰莉 女儿琴
- This is Jack's wife, Teri, and daughter, Kim. - (Kim) Hi.
Hi, Kim. Where do you want us?
-我们要到哪里部署? -一个在里、一个在外
One in and one out.
这里不像是个家 但是也蛮舒服的
Well, it's not exactly home, but it's relatively comfortable.
每隔三十 就有个探测器
There are motion detectors every ten yards.
-我们要在这里住多久? -等我们问话完毕再讨论这个了
- How long do we have to stay here? - We'll worry about that after we debrief you.
-浴室在哪里? -每个房间里都有
- Nina, where's the bathroom? - There's one in each bedroom, through there.
开始前你们俩 可能想先洗个澡
lf you'd both like to clean up before we get started, please do.
验孕片
当时我是参议院中 特别国防委员会的主委
l was the head of the Special Defense Appropriations Committee in the Senate,
那其实就是 偷袭行动的代名词
which is just a euphemism for covert operations.
三年前中情局 向我提报一件事
Three years ago, the ClA brought to my attention
就是科索沃的 维克多杜瑞森所犯下的暴行
atrocities committed by Victor Drazen in Kosovo.
屠杀，酷刑，种族屠杀
Massacres, torture, ethnic cleansing.
他简直是个禽兽 却逐渐受到支持
The man was a monster, and was gaining support.
我透过正常管道干预 配合的速度却很缓慢
l tried to go through the usual channels, but l couldn't get anyone to work quickly enough.
结果我找了一个我知道 可以把事情办好的人去完成
So l contacted the one person l knew who could get the job done,
先把他停职
have him terminated, off the books.
-就是罗伯艾里斯 -没错
- And that would be Robert Ellis. - That's right.
艾里斯透过 我的委员会资助
Ellis was funded through a discretionary fund of my committee.
他的工作就是偷袭行动 并确保不会有人知道是谁干的
His job was to implement the covert missions and see to it that no names were leaked.
所以我们俩 现在都是别人的目标
Now we're both on somebody's list.
这就是 那天的结果要反扑了
So this is payback for what happened that day.
这样的道理才说的过去
lt's the only thing that makes sense.
要是有人 会把我们俩的名字放在一起
But if someone could put your name and my name on a list together,
那他应该也会把 罗伯艾里斯放进来
that means they should be able to find Robert Ellis, too.
你说的对
You're right.
4个6
Four sixes.
翻开吧
Let's see 'em.
我知道 看你的眼睛我就知道了
l knew it! l saw it in your eyes!
你要真的看我眼睛就知道一切 你会爬到大石头下去大哭一场的
lf you could read what's in my eyes, you'd crawl under a rock and cry.
再来一次
Go again.
(phone rings)
巴比，我是大卫派默
- Ellis. - Bobby, it's David Palmer.
-开什么玩笑 -不开玩笑，我在杰克鲍尔旁边
- You gotta be kidding. - l'm not. l'm here with Jack Bauer.
你滚开
Get lost.
在鲍尔旁边?我一直很努力的 不想让你们俩认识
What are you doin' with Bauer? l went to a lot of trouble to make sure you two never met.
但是维克多杜瑞森里面的人 还是把我们连在一起了
Someone close to Victor Drazen seems to have connected us.
-讲清楚一点 -有人要杀我
- Explain. - Someone wants me dead.
看起来也不放过鲍尔 就在今天
And it appears they want Bauer, too. Today.
暗夜行动刚满两周年
The two-year anniversary of Nightfall.
我是唯一知道 你们俩有关联的人
l'm the only one who knows you both were involved.
不会吧，若我们俩都在名单上 你也不会被漏掉
Apparently not. And if we're on the list, it's likely you are, too.
-让我跟鲍尔讲话 -巴比请讲
- Let me talk to Bauer. - l'm right here, Bob.
杰克 你还在反恐小组吗
- Jack. You still at CTU? - Yeah.
我们得互相帮助 好找出凶手
To source this we need each other's help.
很不幸的，过去的12小时内 我要作些牺牲
Unfortunately, over the last 12 hours, l've had to cut a few corners.
现在我被侦讯 乖乖就范
l'm being investigated right now. My hands are tied.
叫他们放了你 大卫会帮你的
Well, get them untied. David can help you there.
可能是你的人 之中最有嫌疑...
lt has to be someone either connected to your team...
我的人根本不知道 参议员的事
No. No one on my team knew of the senator's involvement.
那就一定是 杜瑞森的人了
Well, then it has to be Drazen's group.
我去调暗夜行动的资料 里面有杜瑞森相关的人名
l'll retrieve the closed file on Nightfall. lt'll contain the names of Drazen's associates.
目前你应该 要先查出那笔钱的来路
That'll take a few minutes. Meantime, you need to pick up a trail on the money.
最有可能是从比利时来的 从你那里可以进入帐户查看吗
Odds are it's funded through Belgium. Can you get to your K-3 accounts from there?
-要是我被复职就可以 -好，马上开始
- Yes, if l get reinstated. - All right, start there.
待会儿联络时我们对对看名字 我要怎么联络你
We'll compare names when we talk again. Where can l reach you?
打到反恐小组 洛杉矶办公室找我
CTU, Los Angeles office.
All right.
(knock at door)
(Nina) Teri?
- Yes? - l put some clean clothes on the bed.
我在床上 放了些乾净的衣服
谢谢你
Thank you.
他们说你不走了 我们不是要到内华达去的吗
They called me and said you decided not to fly out. Aren't we going to Nevada?
不去了，参议员有些事要处里 他认为这里是最安全的
Apparently not. The senator needed to do something. He thought we'd be safest here.
-你会搭上下一班飞机吗? -希望会
- Are you taking a later flight? - l don't know. l hope so.
回电给时代杂志，说我接受电访 只有45分钟
Call the Times. Tell them l'll do that phoner, 45 minutes.
Sure.
(dials out)
-你想念我吗? -当然了
- Hello. - You miss me yet?
-不必去内华达了 -我正想订机票了
- Of course. - l hope you didn't bookyour flight to Nevada.
l was just about to. Why?
-为什么 -可能会不去呀
We might not be going.
-几时可以知道呢? -再一个小时吧
- When will you know? - ln about an hour.
要是你留下来 你会留在饭店吗
lf you stay in town, will you remain at the hotel?
不知道 可能会换地方确保安全
l don't know. They might switch us for security reasons.
我会告诉你 我在哪里的
Either way, l'll let you know where l am.
我还闻得到 你的香水味呢
l can still smellyour perfume on my skin.
我一确定就会告诉你
l'll call you as soon as l know.
是那个女的吗
- ls that the girl? - Yes.
派默可能 根本就不离开
Palmer might not be leaving after all.
这样比较好
- Better for us. - Mm-hm.
除掉甘恩斯的人 有什么问题吗?
Was there any problem getting rid of Gaines's people?
No.
根本就不该用他的 早就说过这样大错特错
You should never have used him. l told you it was a mistake.
好，你来弭补 现在行动吧
Fine. You fixed the mistake, now let's move on.
(girl giggles)
她看起来好像玛提娜
She looks like Martina.
安德里，妹妹已经死了
Our sister's dead, Andre.
不要再提了
Leave it alone.
-你找过霍凡和密斯科了吗? -他们正追踪着目标
- Have you spoken to Jovan and Mishko? - They have their targets in sight.
派默这件事我答应你 午夜之前他死定了
And as for Palmer, l give you my word he will be dead by midnight.
-有牙膏吗? -在这里
- Hey. Do you have any toothpaste? - Yeah, it's right there.
这没什么 医生只是要我多小心一点
That's nothing. The doctor just wanted me to take it as a precaution.
吓死我了
You scared me.
Kim.
What?
你怀孕了
You're pregnant.
我不懂，怎么会呢?
l don't understand. What happened today... How is that possible?
当然是跟爸爸，这种验孕 通常要受孕一段时间后...
lt was Dad, of course, but a test like this, it takes time before...
你想再生个小孩 却没告诉过我?
You were trying to have a kid and didn't tell me?
不，亲爱的 事情不是这样的
No, honey, it wasn't like that.
Kim. Kim!
- What? - Please!
我和你一样非常震惊
This is just as much a shock to me as it is to you.
我们都有在避孕 虽然也不一定完全有效
Dad and l use birth control. lt's protection, but it's never 100%.
你不需要我答应
Whatever. You don't need my permission.
我不是要你答应
l'm not asking for your permission, Kimberly.
有时候 你得体谅别人所经历的
Once in a while, you have to think about what another person is going through.
我刚发现我怀孕了
Honey, l just found out l'm pregnant.
难道我不会害怕吗?
You don't think that terrifies me?
会的
Well, it does.
Mom...
对不起
l'm sorry.
这名单上 有你认识的名字吗
(Ellis) Are there any other names on the HK list thatyou recognise?
-里奇果恩，麦可瑞德门 -他们在行动结束前仍有嫌疑
- Rich Goen, Michael Redman. That's it. - No, they weren't cleared until after the op.
-现在有什么我们就用什么 -我不该来的
- l'll use what we have so far. - l shouldn't be here.
-葛琳要我做些事 -我已经取消了
- Green's got me on priority. - l cleared it.
巴比，他来了
- OK, Bob, he's here. - Milo.
-你是谁? -不必管
- Yeah. Who are you? - Don't worry about me.
我看到你 把国防反间线路打开了
Ah, l see you opened some sockets up to Ml5.
-你怎么知道这些 -不必管
- How did you know that? - Doesn't matter.
我得找出一些人名 我会帮你的
We're tryin' to hook up some names. l'm gonna help you.
你的登录名称和密码
Now, what's your login lD and password?
给他吧
Give it to him.
登录名称是LFN
The login lD is LFN.
密码fOOthill94022
Password's foothill 94022.
密码是小写的
Lower case.
等一下
OK, hang on.
找到一部分的资料了
OK, looks like we got some partial results.
-一部分? -还有其他部分不见了
- Partial? - Yeah. Looks like there's something missing.
什么意思?
What do you mean, Bob?
有些东西被拿掉了
Something's been removed.
我来看看
l'll look into it.
麦罗，我先送一个档案 到你的伺服器
Meanwhile, Milo, l'm gonna... l'm gonna send a file to your server.
你去列印出来 给杰克和大卫
Why don't you print out hard copies for Jack and David?
-好呀 -谢了，麦罗
- Yeah. Sure. - Thanks, Milo.
送去了
All right, here we go.
我简直要饿得抓狂了
Feels like l haven't eaten in years.
感觉真好，对不对? 不必再害怕了
Feels good, doesn't it? Not being afraid any more.
Yeah.
妈，对不起 我以前好笨
l'm sorry, Mom, l was being really stupid before.
你几时才要告诉爸爸?
So, when are you gonna tell Dad?
你知道吗?
You know what?
就是现在
Right now. Come on.
Um...
(phone rings)
-反恐小组，我是艾尔梅达 -我是泰莉鲍尔
- CTU. Almeida. - Hi, Tony, it's Teri Bauer calling.
-杰克在吗? -他在，可是非常的忙碌
- Could l talk to Jack, please? - Hi, Teri. Actually, it's a bad time.
- He's... he's kinda busy right now. - Could you tell him to call? lt's important.
可以请他回电吗? 重要的事
好的
Sure.
-我真想看看他会有什么反应 -有你在真好
- l really want to hear his reaction. - l'm so lucky to have you.
Aw, baby.
我们必须开始问话 反恐小组很想知道你们的事情
Hi. Sorry, but we need to start the debrief. CTU's eager to find out what you know.
我们准备好了
- We're ready, huh? - Yeah.
泰莉，就先从你开始吧
- Great. l'd like to start with just you, Teri. - Fine.
-我先到房间里去 -你应该休息一下
- l think l'm gonna go to my room. - That's a good idea. You should try and rest.
这只是标准程序 我们会把你录影下来
This is standard procedure. We're gonna put you on videotape.
OK.
( ''Clocks Grow Old'' by lAm Spoonbender)
(phone rings)
- Yeah? - Hi, Rick?
Hey.
-你还好吗? -还好，只是有点流血
- Kim. - Are you OK?
Yeah. l just lost a little blood.
你得看医生 听起来不太好
You need to see a doctor. You don't sound good.
-我只需要休息几天就好 -去自首吧，可以去治疗
- l just need a few days' rest. - Turn yourself in. You can get medical help.
我会被逮捕的
And l'll also get arrested.
是你帮我们脱逃的 我会告诉他们的
- But you helped us escape. l'll tell them that. - No!
不要向他们提到我
Don't tell them anything about me.
我妈妈正接受问话 他们一定会问到你的
Well, it's too late. My mom's already being questioned. They're gonna ask about you.
我是下一个 我不会说谎
l'm next. l can't lie.
好，不要说谎
OK. Don't.
告诉他们 我不知道是什么事情
Tell them that l didn't know anything about what was goin' on
而且我被丹威胁 他手上有枪
and that Dan threatened me, he had a gun.
好，答应我你要来自首
OK, but promise me you'll turn yourself in.
我得好好想一想，我不像你 我不是来自好家庭的
l gotta think this through. l'm not like you, Kim. l don't come from a good family.
司法制度 不会放过我的
- System's not gonna give me a break. - lt's your only way out of this, Rick.
这是你唯一的路呀
我带你到甘恩斯那儿 那是绑架
l brought you to Gaines. That's kidnapping.
他们会送我去 坐牢一辈子的
They could put me in jail for the rest of my life.
这些事情 与我参选毫无关联
What's incredible is that none of this has anything to do with me running for president.
与这次的初选也无关
lt has nothing to do with... the primary.
更与我的肤色无关
lt has nothing to do with my being black.
这只是来自 对付维克多杜瑞森的复仇
lt's just revenge for taking out... Victor Drazen.
Yes, sir.
(phone rings)
大卫，是我
- Hello. - David, it's Sherry.
-你回到饭店了吗 -对，你在哪里
- Oh, hi. Are you back at the hotel? - Yes. Where are you?
我在反恐小组 政府机关
l'm at CTU, a government agency.
为什么?
Why?
-我要处理一些事情 -怎么一回事?
- There's some things l have to take care of. - David, what's going on?
我在调查 是谁想要暗杀我
l'm trying to find out who's attempting to kill me, Sherry.
我得走了，在饭店等我
- l've got to go. Wait for me at the hotel. OK? - OK.
再见
Bye.
事情怎么停不下来
Just doesn't stop.
对整件事我感到遗憾
l'm sorry this is happening to you, sir.
你被拘留了
You've been detained.
你的家人也被绑架
Your family's been kidnapped.
可是你却仍关心我
And you're concerned about me.
那是与选举无关的事 是我儿子的事情
That didn't have anything to do with the election. That was about my son.
他还好吗?
ls he OK?
我今天才发现
l just realised today...
我经常都没有 陪在他身旁
that l haven't always been there for him.
更要命的是
And what's killing me...
他无时无刻 都支持着我
is that he's always been there for me.
当政治人物的儿子 很不容易
Being the son of a politician isn't easy.
当个儿子，或女儿
Being a son... or a daughter...
或是父亲
or a father...
也都很不容易
none of it's easy.
你太太和女儿都好吗?
Your wife and daughter OK?
不知道
l don't know.
应该还好吧
l hope so.
放轻松 我只有几个问题
- OK. Just try to be relaxed. - OK.
l just have a few questions.
这是艾里斯传来的 我把它分为三部分
This just came in from Ellis. l organised it into three sections.
第一部分是所有参照资料 接下来是暗夜计画的简要内容
Cross-references are in the first part. Then there's a summary of Operation Nightfall.
比较不重要的细节 放在最后
Details that may not be important are at the end.
-不见的资料有下落吗? -还没有
- Any word on the missing file? - No, not yet.
好，谢谢你，麦罗
OK, thanks, Milo.
驻利比亚大使 怎么也在上面?
What is the Ambassador to Libya doing on this list?
可能是把资助杜瑞森的钱 与政府的钱分开吧
Probably kept Drazen's money separate from the government.
我们注意他一段时间
We've had our eye on him for quite some time.
有听过一个 瑞尼邦尼尔吗?
Do you know a Rene Bonniere?
-那是谁? -他从北非来的
- No. Who's he? - He's out of North Africa.
分区上级觉得 他想在美国进行恐怖活动
A couple high-ups over at District thought he was trying to set up terrorist cells in the US.
杰克，看第四页
Jack. Page four.
第二段下面
Second paragraph down.
杜瑞森的妻女 也在沙堡里
Drazen's wife and daughter were in the bunker?
你知道这件事吗? 之前的报告没提到这件事
Did you know about this? This wasn't in our initial report.
她们被炸死了
They died in the explosion.
天哪
My God.
这是以牙还牙 因为我们杀了杜瑞森一家人
This is an eye for an eye. We took out Drazen and his family.
现在他们想杀我家人
Now someone wants mine.
是谁 在保护你的家人?
Who's in charge of protecting your family?
谁有权力 加派安全人员保护她们?
Jack! Who has the authority to add security to your wife and daughter?
查裴尔
Chapelle.
-参议员有什么事? -马上去叫查裴尔先生
- (woman) Yes, Senator? - Send in Mr Chapelle right away.
Yes, sir.
你没办法观察到 任何有关他们计画的一切吗?
There was nothing else you saw or heard that gave you a glimpse into their operation?
不 在我们面前他们不多说
No, that's it. They really didn't talk much in front of us.
谈谈关於那个叫瑞克的男孩 他帮了你吗?
- Tell me about this boy Rick. He helped you? - Yeah.
怎么帮?
How?
各种方法，最重要是他给我们 一把枪还帮我们逃跑
Well, different ways, but mainly he gave us a gun and he helped us escape.
-他怎么会有枪的 -不知道
- How'd he get a gun? - l don't know.
知道他姓什么吗?
- And you don't know his last name? - No.
-我想琴也不知道的 -她们怎么认识的?
- l don't think Kimberly knows either. - How did she meet him?
透过她的朋友 珍娜约克
Through her friend, Janet York.
大家都说 "等你女儿变成青少年
Everyone used to say ''Wait until she's a teenager,
你就知道担心的滋味了"
you'll finally understand the meaning of the word 'worry'.''
我相信她会长大的 杰克说她头脑很清醒
l'm sure she'll grow out of it. Jack says she's basically a level-headed kid.
杰克会提到琴吗?
Jack talks about Kim?
会说些平常的事情
Just the usual stuff.
我很吃惊，他的工作看来 总是严肃而且秘密
lt surprises me. Jack's work always seems so serious and secretive.
很难想像他坐在办公室 与你们谈论家里的事
lt's hard to picture him sitting around the office talking about his family.
有时候中午 他想到些事情就会讲
Sometimes at lunch he'll bring up something if something's on his mind.
你认为瑞克对 犯罪首脑甘恩斯了解吗
So, do you think Rick had the confidence of lra Gaines, the leader of the group?
这我也不清楚
l really couldn't tell you that.
妮娜 可以请问你个问题吗?
- Nina, could l ask you a question? - Sure.
我与杰克分居的时候
When Jack and l were separated...
他有提到过我吗?
did he ever talk about me?
杰克从来不谈 婚姻的事情
Jack never discussed his marriage.
他只是有时候会提到琴
Oh.
Sometimes he would... talk about Kim,
you know.
我们都知道 他正面临一些困难
We all knew he was going through a very hard time
而且他非常想念你们俩
and that he missed you both very much.
后来我们复合的时候 他提到过曾经与人交往过
When Jack and l got back together again... he told me that he'd been with someone else.
我说我们分居这段时间的事情 我不会在乎的
l told him it didn't matter what l did, what he did... when we were apart -
重要的是 我们从新开始之后的事
that was in the past. The only thing that mattered was what we did from that point on.
那个人就是你对不对?
lt was you, wasn't it?
Teri.
我们下直升机的时候 我就知道了
l saw it... when we got off the helicopter.
你看他的眼神不一样
l saw it when you looked at him.
在你们分居后
After you were separated,
是的，我们有交往过
yes, we saw each other.
但是也不太久，他觉得错了 所以他回到你身旁
But it didn't last long. He realised it was a mistake and he went back to you.
你认为呢?
- What about you? - What about me?
你会认为他错了吗?
Did you think it was a mistake?
你仍然和他上床吗?
- Are you still sleeping with him? - No.
Teri...
他回到你身边之前就结束了 是真的
it was over before he went back to you. That is the truth.
我知道这时候 发现这一切你会很难过
Look, l realise this is a terrible time for you to discover all this.
不然什么时候 才是好时候呢
When do you think a good time would be, Nina?
抱歉
l'm sorry.
我们必须把口供问完
lt's just we have to get through the rest of this.
我想休息一下
l need to take a break.
五分钟后我们就要走了
Yeah, Mike, l know. We'll be leaving in about five minutes.
不等艾里斯了 我要走了
l can't wait for Ellis. l've got to go.
他们不会让我在这里工作 技术上我仍是在被捕状态中
Senator, they're not gonna let me continue to work here. l am technically still under arrest.
Come on.
Ryan!
-参议员，有事吗? -听说你们逮捕了杰克
- Yes, Senator? - l understand you have Jack under arrest.
我告诉参议员 我目前被拘留中
l told the senator l was being detained.
眼前的危机比他可能 犯下的任何过错都更严重
There is an ongoing crisis that supersedes any charges that might be filed against him.
我要求你们 马上把他复职
- But Senator... - l want him reinstated immediately.
长官，你无权决定这个的
Sir, you don't have the authority to make that decision.
Alberta, please.
长官，您的要求恕无法从命 鲍尔的罪状是非常严重的
Sir, what you are asking isn't possible. The charges against Agent Bauer are serious.
要是我们不听证就让他复职 就是藐视整个单位的规定
We'd be in contempt of agency regulations if we reinstated him without a hearing.
我不需要正式的复职
Ryan, you don't have to reinstate me. Not permanently.
这里没有人 比我对整个状况更了解
Nobody here has as much information about this situation as l do.
只要今天给我 暂时的身份就好了
Give me provisional status till the end of the day.
之后你们还是可以拘留我
Then you can take me back into custody, do whatever you want.
好，杰克
Fine, Jack.
你在反恐小组之外进行 但是你得对我负责
You work the case out of CTU, but you answer to me.
参议员 祝您选举好运
Good luck with your campaign, Senator.
Thank you.
陪我一起走
Walk with me.
特勤组要我离开加州 他们说这里不安全
Secret Service wants me to leave the state. They say it's not safe.
我也这么认为
Well, l agree with them.
我很清楚杜瑞森的人都到了 而且他们今天就会行动
The one thing we know... is that Drazen's people are here, and they want us today.
现在也快三点了 今天也过了一大半了
And it's almost three o'clock now. The day is more than half over.
我要留下来
l'm going to stay.
让我把他们引出来 再来好好对付他们
Let's flush them out into the open and deal with them.
不然你我的家人们
Otherwise you and l and our families
会是我们这辈子的遗憾
will be looking over our shoulders for the rest of our lives.
我懂，我会找艾里斯 有消息会通知你
l understand. l'll follow up with Ellis. l'll keep you posted.
你知道如何找到我的
- You know how to get in touch with me. - Jack.
对不起我误会了你
l'm sorry that l misjudged you.
谢谢你，参议员
Thank you, Senator.
Excuse me.
我妈妈来到之前，没有人理我 我被关起来了
Before my mom came, nobody talked to me. They put me in the room, l was locked in.
那瑞克呢?
- What about Rick? - Rick? What about Rick?
-他是绑架你的人之一，是吗? -也不全然
- Well, he was one of your kidnappers, right? - Not exactly.
他与丹一起 把你交给甘恩斯的
l thought he and Dan brought you to Gaines?
其实主要是丹 不是瑞克
Well, it was mostly Dan. l mean, not Rick.
当他知道是什么事 他也吓了一大跳
l think he was actually just as surprised as we were about what was happening.
真的吗?
Really?
对 他一直都在跟丹吵架
Well, yeah. He was fighting with Dan the entire time.
他还帮助我们逃跑
He actually helped us escape.
不要讲得太快
Hold on. Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
(phone rings)
等一下
Hold on.
-我是麦尔 -哈罗，是我
- Myers. - Hey, it's me.
查裴尔暂时让我复职 是派默要求的
Chapelle reinstated me to provisional status for the rest of the day, at Palmer's request.
-太好了 -那边情况如何?
- That's great, Jack. - Yeah. How's everything going over there?
还好
- Not bad. - Look, we're sending over two more teams.
我们还要另派两组人 看来泰莉与琴也是目标之一
- Why? - Looks like Teri and Kim were targets as well.
但是不要让她们知道
Nina... this is not information they need to know, OK?
-当然了 -我和泰莉讲个话
- No, of course. - Good, thanks.
- Let me speak to Teri, OK? - Sure.
Teri?
杰克打来的
lt's Jack.
嗨，亲爱的 你还好吗?
- Hi, Jack. - Hey, sweetheart. You OK? How you doin'?
我还可以
l'm OK.
-那么琴呢? -她很好
- How's Kim? - She's fine.
东尼说你有重要的事 要告诉我
Tony gave me a message that you wanted to tell me something important.
没什么大不了的
No, it's nothing important.
真的吗? 听起来怪怪的
Are you sure? You sound funny.
没什么，只是...
lt's nothing, l just...
l just...
我好累
l'm so tired.
试着休息一下
Why don't you try and get some rest, sweetheart?
这房子里 你需要什么的话
Listen, if... if you need anything from the house, Nina will make sure
妮娜会帮你找人去取的
- someone can go and get it for you, OK? - Yeah, OK.
得走了，我爱你 我会再打电话给你
l've gotta go. l love you, OK? l'll call you as soon as l can.
OK. Bye-bye.
我马上就回来
Mom!
l'll be right back.
-说了些什么? -我没告诉他
- So, what did he say? - l didn't tell him.
-怎么不说? -时间不对
- Why not? - lt wasn't the right time.
你应该回去找妮娜 把话讲完
You should go back and finish with Nina, honey.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
没有，我只是觉得你得回去 让妮娜把话问完
Nothing. l just think you should finish answering Nina's questions.
(phone rings)
杰克，我是巴比
Bauer.
- Jack, it's Bob. - Hey, Bob.
我又传了一些资料给麦罗 但是不见的资料还找不到
Yeah, l shot over a few more things to Milo, but l still can't locate the missin' file.
-我帮得上忙吗? -给麦罗的资料够你试试看
- How can l help? - l gave Milo enough to try it on your end.
这些档案我越看越觉得 那些资料是故意被拿掉的
The more l look at this thing, the more l'm convinced the file was taken out deliberately.
所以我认为 我们要找的东西就在里面
Which leads me to believe... it contains what we're lookin' for.
你猜得出来 档案是几时被偷的吗
Can you give an estimate of when you think the file was stolen?
还有哪些人 会有资格动这东西呢
Also a list of people you think could've had access to even get in there?
还不知道，告诉麦罗 我找到一个方法...
Not yet, but you tell Milo l got some ideas on how to...
Urgh!
Bob?
听得到吗?
Can you hear me?
Bob?
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=- 时间轴微调:-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组 时间轴组=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径 web-dl版本时间轴调节:dizhang
Visiontext Subtitles: Kerrie Slavin
ENGLlSH SDH